https://www.speld.org.nz/privacy-statement

HomeContact UsServicesOur ServicesDiagnostic AssessmentOne-on-one TuitionTeacher CredentialsTrainingFinancial SupportMembership SupportStoriesNews & EventsNewsEventsAbout UsAbout SPELD NZOur Vision & ValuesOur HistoryOur ApproachOur SupportersAnnual ReportsMoodle Login
HomeContact UsServicesOur ServicesDiagnostic AssessmentOne-on-one TuitionTeacher CredentialsTrainingFinancial SupportMembership SupportStoriesNews & EventsNewsEventsAbout UsAbout SPELD NZOur Vision & ValuesOur HistoryOur ApproachOur SupportersAnnual ReportsMoodle LoginMembership Application  Information Pack
DONATEChildrenServices for ChildrenKey Indicators for ChildrenSLD DefinitionsAdultsServices for AdultsKey Indicators for AdultsSLD DefinitionsEducatorsEmployers Privacy StatementHome » Privacy Statement Privacy PolicySPELD NZ respects the privacy and confidentiality of all our members and clients. We are committed to our requirements under the Privacy Act 1993. We collect personal information provided by you when you register with us to use our services and general website data generated by our onsite systems. The website information does not identify you personally and is not linked to the personal information you may have provided.Information SharingWe use your personal information to process your requests or transactions and to keep you informed about upcoming events, services or other information that may be of interest to you. Your personally identifiable information will only be shared with third parties when we have your consent or believe in good faith that we are required to do so by law. SPELD NZ will not sell or supply your information to any other third parties.Information StorageSPELD NZ holds personal information in a combination of secure computer and network storage facilities and paper-based files. We take steps to protect the personal information we hold from misuse, loss, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.Use of CookiesWe use Google Analytics to help analyse how users are using our website. This information is not personally identifiable and is not shared with any third party. We gather the information through the use of cookies. A cookie is a small file that resides on your computer and is recognised by our server when you visit our site. If you do not wish to have cookies placed on your computer, you can disable them at any time from your web browser. This will disable cookies from all sources, not just our website unless otherwise noted. You can opt out of our tracking cookies without affecting your ability to use our website.Opting in and opting outYou will always have the option to opt in to our services and to opt out of those services at any stage. This means you may change your mind at any stage about participating in any of our member services.Your rightsYou have the right to access and correct your personal information held by SPELD NZ. Please contact us for access to your information, or if you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy.Our Website Contact is nationaloffice@speld.org.nzHe mea rehita ne te Mana Tohu Matauranga o Aotearoa kia tu hei Wahi Whakangungu Motuhake i raro i te maru o te Ture Matauranga 1989 me ona menemana. Contact UsStoriesNews & EventsAbout UsSitemapServices for:ChildrenAdultsEducatorsEmployersInformation Pack Membership Application Charities number: CC46602 SPELD NZ is a certified NZQA provider Privacy statement
